<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comingsoons on Abide Ministries</title>
    <link>https://abide.community/comingsoon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comingsoons on Abide Ministries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://abide.community/comingsoon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kids Empowered on the Move</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/comingsoon/kidsempoweredonthemove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/comingsoon/kidsempoweredonthemove/</guid>
      <description>Oakland County is one of the wealthiest counties in the United States, a community where one would believe those in need could find easy access to resources. Yet, even in the midst of wealth, certain people and communities can find it very difficult to get access to basic needs and valuable relationships due to factors like generational poverty, racial discrimination, literacy struggles, mental and physical sickness, and more. The children of these adults struggling with poverty can be even more at risk, with over 2,000 children in Oakland County considered homeless at the beginning of 2022, and many more on the cusp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Or More</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/comingsoon/twoormore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/comingsoon/twoormore/</guid>
      <description>For decades, a those who identify as bi/multi-racial have been overlooked within society. Whether in families, neighborhoods, communities of faith, or otherwise, these individuals are often seen as &amp;ldquo;half&amp;rdquo; of one idenity and &amp;ldquo;half&amp;rdquo; of another, and as such are rarely fully embraced. This &amp;ldquo;half existence&amp;rdquo; leads to bullying, disillusionment, poor mental health, and a host of other issues that do not reflect God&amp;rsquo;s desires for their lives, which is all the more concerning when one considers that those who identify as bi/multi-racial will be the majority of people in the United States by 2040.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
