<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on Abide Ministries</title>
    <link>https://abide.community/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on Abide Ministries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://abide.community/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Captain</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/captain/</guid>
      <description>There are some significant issues in the American financial planning industry. Many of the people who need help can’t afford it and others who can afford it often get taken advantage of through excessive investment advisory fees, investment commissions, loads on mutual funds, and excessive fund expenses just to name a few. Correcting these issues takes someone bold enough to offer something unprecedented and with as little bias as possible: free financial planning and education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/motion/</guid>
      <description>In December 2004, at age 41, Karen Rohner became a widow. In an instant, she went from being a happy mother and wife to a confused, scared and lonely widow and single mom of 2 teenagers. She found the only thing harder than dealing with losing her husband was watching her kids grieve and suffer from the loss of their father.
Through a series of fortunate connections, Karen was introduced to 4 other young widows who also recently lost their husbands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pearl</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/pearl/</guid>
      <description>Yang Chen is the founder of Pearl, a relational network designed to help Asian Americans flourish in Christ.
Yang immigrated to the US at the age of 5 for his father’s PhD program at Oakland University. He quickly found himself being influenced by two very different cultures. At home, his family’s Chinese culture established the norm, but at school and with peers, American youth culture provided a very different outlook and influence on his life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
