<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abide Ministries</title>
    <link>https://abide.community/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Abide Ministries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://abide.community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/about/</guid>
      <description>WHAT IT MEANS TO ABIDE In the last few years, Abide Ministries has expanded its reach by helping to start and sustain new initiatives that help people intimately know the love of God. Taken together, these initiatives are known as the Abide Collective. Some collective ministries serve human trafficking victims, others semi-professional athletes, individual and community needs through art and reconciliation, and still others international students, helping each person they encounter to hear from God just as we desire to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/donate/</guid>
      <description>Help us help others. As the Abide Collective has grown, we at Abide Ministries realize how important it is for us to be able to help our Collective members as much as we can. We have such a diverse group of families and individuals doing work in a variety of contexts, some of whom struggle to find the necessary funds to do the important and meaningful work that Jesus has given them to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70x7</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/70x7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/70x7/</guid>
      <description>Over several years, Donna McCauley has developed friendships with men and women on the streets of Detroit and families who need encouragement in their faith. Donna, along with her 70x7 team of friends who have a long term commitment to encouraging others, spend time with these individuals and families on a weekly basis. Encouragement is given in the form of friendship, dignity, bible study, prayer and the meeting of a few basic needs, all with the view of helping individuals and families navigate away from at-risk activities and toward Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beholders</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/beholders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/beholders/</guid>
      <description>Since 2013 Beholders has been training believers on how to cultivate a life that attracts the presence of God and to walk in a lifestyle of Spirit-led evangelism. Led by Aaron and Adrianne Jackson, Beholders believes to grow as a messenger one must go out and share the message. It’s in the mission field that people learn to partner with the Holy Spirit and get set free from fear.
Beholders trains by creating worship opportunities where believers can come behold the Father’s heart, because they believe when one beholds something, one becomes like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champion</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/champion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/champion/</guid>
      <description>Champion exists to help local professional and amateur athletes encounter the love and truth of Christ in order to help them become fully devoted followers of Jesus. Through Bible studies, Sunday gatherings, friendly hospitality, and individual mentoring, Champion provides real friendship and Christ-centered life guidance to players in local professional baseball leagues, with plans to expand to more sports in the near future.
Launched in 2016 by Tony DeMonaco, Champion now has 10 chaplains who work with young men in the United Shore Professional Baseball League, an independent professional league headquartered in Utica, MI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivate</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/cultivate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/cultivate/</guid>
      <description>David-Chad Svenson is the director of Cultivate, a ministry devoted to developing people, plans, and prayer support to grow God&amp;rsquo;s Kingdom. He began working with Cultivate in the summer of 2013 because of his heart for discipleship and men’s ministry, as well as his gift for shepherding and teaching. He has helped Cultivate develop trainings and classes, while also mentoring several young men through one-on-one relationships and men’s small groups. He now leads a team of volunteer mentors and student leaders who endeavor to transform the people of Oakland University into kingdom workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Sea</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/kingdomsea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/kingdomsea/</guid>
      <description>Empowering and equipping Christians to help others follow Jesus and make disciples of all the nations is at the heart of Kingdom Sea.
With a heart for individuals of all nations, Kingdom Sea looks to inspire Christians to create intentional friendships and mentorships with the people of all backgrounds and ethnicities, including international students in their own geographic area.
Discipleship begins with authentic relationships and being intentional to reach out to and come alongside others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patron</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/patron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/patron/</guid>
      <description>Working with national anti-sex trafficking organizations, and under the auspices of both federal and local law enforcement, Patron works to simultaneously end the demand of domestic sex-trafficking via tangible, direct, and effective action for men in local communities while creatively serving the local eco-system of various anti-sex trafficking organizations in order to help prolong their combined and comprehensive sustainability.
A definition of “patron” is simply, “a person who buys goods or uses the services of an establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconcile</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/reconcile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/reconcile/</guid>
      <description>This world often feels like a battle between us and them. We look for people who are like us, who look like us, who like what we would like, and who make us feel comfortable. Meanwhile, we are constantly categorizing the people who don’t fit the definition of us as “them”. “Them” is whoever is not like us, for all the reasons that we believe. Whether conscious or unconscious, we are looking for ways to define our world so we know the difference between us and them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restoring</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/restoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/restoring/</guid>
      <description>Joshua and Yvette Rock have been living in Detroit for the past 16 years, building friendships and raising their family, hoping to witness and encourage God’s restoration among the people and in the neighborhoods of Detroit. Restoring has developed out of this desire, as a way to support and encourage friends in the process of believing, following, submitting, and abiding in Jesus. As Joshua and Yvette share life with their friends in the city, they work to strengthen marriages and families, meet with men and women, and serve their neighbors in practical ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transplanters</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/transplanters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/transplanters/</guid>
      <description>Transplanters enables pioneering non-profit leaders to take the next step in their growth and development. These leaders are pioneers because they sacrifice everything in pursuit of their innovative ideas. Transplanters serves these leaders by performing development services including grant writing and consulting on organizational structure, systems, and priorities.
In addition, Transplanters serves foundations by providing exceptional project management and reporting, as well as the opportunity to align with well-managed, highly-influential non-profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vessel</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/vessel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/vessel/</guid>
      <description>In the spring of 2018, Charli Carnill felt the call of Jesus to leave her collegiate softball career and community of friends at Cornerstone University in order to offer herself as a servant to those suffering the effects of poverty and injustice all over the world. While a vessel describes any container which carries something, Charli&amp;rsquo;s desire is to be a vessel which carries the love of Christ to those who may be struggling to find it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application development</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom website design</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO &amp; SEM services</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress integration</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>