<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abide Ministries</title>
    <link>https://abide.community/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Abide Ministries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 06:12:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abide.community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/about/</guid>
      <description>WHAT IT MEANS TO ABIDE In the last few years, Abide Ministries has expanded its reach by helping to start and sustain new initiatives that help people intimately know the love of God. Taken together, these initiatives are known as the Abide Collective. Some collective ministries serve human trafficking victims, others semi-professional athletes, individual and community needs through art and reconciliation, and still others international students, helping each person they encounter to hear from God just as we desire to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/donate/</guid>
      <description>ONLINE GIFTS Online gifts can be made using the form on this page. You can make one-time or recurring gifts using credit cards, debit cards, or bank transfers. All transactions are processed through Donorbox (a Stripe Partner) for the highest level of security and convenience. Once you make a gift, you can manage your gift at www.donorbox.org.
CHECK GIFTS Check gifts can be made out to: Abide Ministries. Checks can be sent to: PO Box 101, Clawson MI 48017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/explore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/explore/</guid>
      <description>OVERVIEW Join the Abide Collective for an afternoon on the Detroit Riverfront! On Sunday, September 29, You will be able to meet the creative and courageous leaders of the Abide Collective, learn more about the beautiful work they are doing, and build relationships new and old. Entrance is at Cullen Plaza, 1340 Atwater St, Detroit MI. Please enter here, even if you can&amp;rsquo;t park there.
3-4 PM Stroll Each branch of the Abide Collective will be in a different spot along the Riverfront at the new Milliken State Park and Harbor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70x7</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/70x7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/70x7/</guid>
      <description>Over several years, Donna McCauley has developed friendships with men and women on the streets of Detroit and families who need encouragement in their faith. Donna, along with her 70x7 team of friends who have a long term commitment to encouraging others, spend time with these individuals and families on a weekly basis. Encouragement is given in the form of friendship, dignity, bible study, prayer and the meeting of a few basic needs, all with the view of helping individuals and families navigate away from at-risk activities and toward Jesus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>99:1 Ministries</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/99-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/99-1/</guid>
      <description>For over 30 years, Jeff and Anne Henderson have been speaking into the lives of people with the truth of God’s word. By sharing practical life experience, teaching, and coaching, as well as through relational mentoring and discipleship God has allowed them to affect the lives of others in a beautiful way. Through these relationships and experiences, the dream to create 99:1 Ministries was born.
Jeff and Anne are being led by God to begin a ministry that would seek to honor Jesus’ own heart - reaching out to the ones who need to know that the Father’s heart is for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fonte</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/afonte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/afonte/</guid>
      <description>In the developing villages and townships scattered all over Brazil, children struggle to find adequate resources. Food can be scarce, education difficult, and healthcare often unattainable as families are stretched to their breaking points just to ensure the basic needs of life are met. These struggles often blossom into greater societal issues, such as broken families, drug trafficking, human trafficking, and generational poverty, which tend to envelop the lives of the children in the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/captain/</guid>
      <description>There are some significant issues in the American financial planning industry. Many of the people who need help can’t afford it and others who can afford it often get taken advantage of through excessive investment advisory fees, investment commissions, loads on mutual funds, and excessive fund expenses just to name a few. Correcting these issues takes someone bold enough to offer something unprecedented and with as little bias as possible: free financial planning and education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champion</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/champion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/champion/</guid>
      <description>Champion exists to help local professional and amateur athletes encounter the love and truth of Christ in order to help them become fully devoted followers of Jesus. Through Bible studies, Sunday gatherings, friendly hospitality, and individual mentoring, Champion provides real friendship and Christ-centered life guidance to players in local professional baseball leagues, with plans to expand to more sports in the near future.
Launched in 2016 by Tony DeMonaco, Champion now has 10 chaplains who work with young men in the United Shore Professional Baseball League, an independent professional league headquartered in Utica, MI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect the Nations</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/connectthenations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/connectthenations/</guid>
      <description>The roots of Connect the Nations started to grow in Alexa Lawlor from the time she was young. As a high school and college student, Alexa was fascinated and enthused by people from different cultures and backgrounds, going out of her way to meet people and make sure they had a friend while adjusting to life in a new place.
In 2016, Alexa merged her passion for international friends, abilities as a certified language coach, and welcoming spirit to form Connect the Nations, a ministry that exists to see people from all nations connected to Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivate</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/cultivate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/cultivate/</guid>
      <description>Kyle Vens is the director of Cultivate, a ministry devoted to developing Christlike character in university students so they can grow God&amp;rsquo;s kingdom.
After growing in his Christlike character through Cultivate as a college student at Oakland University, Kyle was named director of the ministry in 2019. Kyle&amp;rsquo;s spiritual gifts of shepherding, teaching, and leadership were all shaped over three years as an undergraduate psychology student from 2016-2019, making him a great fit to share his experience with a new generation of college students at Oakland University and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Door of Hope</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/doorofhope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/doorofhope/</guid>
      <description>There are communities in our world where the value of women is determined by men. Unfortunately this arrangement leaves many women in positions of servitude rather than teamwork, destitution rather than support and in oppression rather than flourishing. The result? Millions of women all over the world find themselves abandoned, left to sex slavery, child marriage, female infantacide, homelessness, starvation, and more.
Door of Hope exists to meet women in these places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haiti Children&#39;s Aid Society</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/hcas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/hcas/</guid>
      <description>Haiti Children’s Aid Society USA was established as a branch of Abide Ministries in 2019 to provide support to the orphaned and impoverished children of Mirebalais, Haiti.
Haiti Children’s Aid Society has five major purposes. First, we are committed to relieving poverty by providing basic amenities, medical and health care, and basic social services to orphaned and impoverished children in Haiti. Second, we are invested in improving the quality of life and drinking water in Haiti through construction of wells and water treatment — giving the gift of “living water” for the body, mind and the spirit of every child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEELS Group</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/heels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/heels/</guid>
      <description>Siblings Gina and Joe share a mutual desire to help individuals overcome obstacles caused from trauma due to domestic and sexual abuse as well as helping clients successfully reintegrate into society after involvement with the judicial system. In an effort to defeat these barriers, they co-founded HEELS Group, an organization established to assist individuals in need of assistance with issues related to abuse or reentry. Through their ministry of availability, HEELS aims to assist clients in repurposing their lives through Healing, Empowerment, Education, Leadership training and Success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope For The Nations</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/hopeforthenations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/hopeforthenations/</guid>
      <description>When John Allen began working in college ministry over 25 years ago, the vast majority of the students he met had gone to church growing up or had some sense of who Jesus is and what his teachings say. However, every year since his start, the percentage of students who went to a church has been decreasing. On many campuses that percentage has dropped from 70% to at most 20%. At the same time, most of the college ministries have remained focused on reaching out to the presently Christian student or students who have some church background, creating few opportunities for those who have never encountered the gospel of Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaleo Arts</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/kaleoarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/kaleoarts/</guid>
      <description>For over a decade, Renee Mulliniks and Nancy Zott have made it their mission to help children discover their identity in Christ through arts-based curriculum and programs. Their shared goal has been to help children find what they are good at and know there is a purpose for why they were given that talent, to face their fears and build confidence in a safe and loving environment, and finally to share their stories with others in order to become leaders among their peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Empowered on the Move</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/kidsempoweredonthemove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/kidsempoweredonthemove/</guid>
      <description>Even in one of the wealthiest counties in the United States, those in poverty tend to fall through the cracks, quickly becoming unseen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor Mission</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/mentormission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/mentormission/</guid>
      <description>Mentor Mission was founded on the premise that youth are surrounded by a world that is hurting:
 dysfunctional families loss of peers to suicide a culture that accepts anything respectless education lack of purpose and direction  With these tough circumstances pressing in around them daily, young people hunger for something beautiful and real in the midst of it all. They have a desire to see change happen, and the ability to bring it about in their lifetimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miriam&#39;s Miracle</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/miriamsmiracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/miriamsmiracle/</guid>
      <description>In April of 2017, Phil and Maryanne Munroe traveled on a mission trip to Haiti to help rebuild the nation after Hurricane Matthew, a category 5 storm, caused massive destruction. Little did they know that God had other plans on that trip - more specifically, a plan to rebuild Phil&amp;rsquo;s heart and launch him on a path to help others discover their God-given purpose.
On April 6, 2017, while watching an amazing sunrise over the place where they were staying, Phil surrendered his life to Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motion</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/motion/</guid>
      <description>In December 2004, at age 41, Karen Rohner became a widow. In an instant, she went from being a happy mother and wife to a confused, scared and lonely widow and single mom of 2 teenagers. She found the only thing harder than dealing with losing her husband was watching her kids grieve and suffer from the loss of their father.
Through a series of fortunate connections, Karen was introduced to 4 other young widows who also recently lost their husbands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Your Feet Detroit</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/onyourfeetdetroit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/onyourfeetdetroit/</guid>
      <description>There are thousands of people experiencing homelessness in Detroit. Beyond their obvious needs, homelessness leads to feelings of loneliness and isolation. During the winter months, they face even greater hardships trying to survive the brutal cold weather.
Led by local couple Anthony and Lauren Guastella, On Your Feet Detroit began with a small group of friends handing out essential items to keep people warm during the harsh winter months. Since these humble beginnings in 2015, the efforts have grown as more people have joined in on the mission and more friends experiencing homelessness have been served.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patron</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/patron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/patron/</guid>
      <description>Working with national anti-sex trafficking organizations, and under the auspices of both federal and local law enforcement, Patron works to simultaneously end the demand of domestic sex-trafficking via tangible, direct, and effective action for men in local communities while creatively serving the local eco-system of various anti-sex trafficking organizations in order to help prolong their combined and comprehensive sustainability.
A definition of “patron” is simply, “a person who buys goods or uses the services of an establishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pearl</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/archive/pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/archive/pearl/</guid>
      <description>Yang Chen is the founder of Pearl, a relational network designed to help Asian Americans flourish in Christ.
Yang immigrated to the US at the age of 5 for his father’s PhD program at Oakland University. He quickly found himself being influenced by two very different cultures. At home, his family’s Chinese culture established the norm, but at school and with peers, American youth culture provided a very different outlook and influence on his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reconcile</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/reconcile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/reconcile/</guid>
      <description>This world often feels like a battle between us and them. We look for people who are like us, who look like us, who like what we would like, and who make us feel comfortable. Meanwhile, we are constantly categorizing the people who don’t fit the definition of us as “them”. “Them” is whoever is not like us, for all the reasons that we believe. Whether conscious or unconscious, we are looking for ways to define our world so we know the difference between us and them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restoring</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/restoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/restoring/</guid>
      <description>Since 2001, Joshua and Yvette Rock have been living in Detroit, building friendships and raising their family, hoping to witness and encourage God’s restoration among the people and in the neighborhoods of Detroit. Restoring has developed out of this desire, as a way to support and encourage friends in the process of believing, following, submitting, and abiding in Jesus. As Joshua and Yvette share life with their friends in the city, they work to strengthen marriages and families, meet with men and women, and serve their neighbors in practical ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUBY™</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/ruby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/ruby/</guid>
      <description>The young women of Gen-Z (ages 10-25) are a force to be reckoned with. They are the most educated, entrepreneurial, empathetic, and value-centered generation the world has ever seen, yet they are collectively in deeper turmoil than most older generations recognize. Any given day these young women face the difficulties of navigating a global pandemic, school shooting epidemic, intense comparison, anxiety/depression, body dysmorphia, low-self esteem from social media and high-stakes cultural tensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanctuary</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/sanctuary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/sanctuary/</guid>
      <description>Those who experience trauma often have a long and difficult road to recovery. Children and teens with trauma histories need even greater attention, as trauma throughout childhood and adolescence can have unique and often lifelong effects. Still, even in the face of the most difficult experiences, interventions from trained trauma therapists can lead to incredible healing in the life of the person affected, especially young people. These therapists have in-depth training specifically designed to aid people who have experienced these sorts of issues, and with their help, those who have suffered experience great redemption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tatlow Society</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/thetatlowsociety/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/thetatlowsociety/</guid>
      <description>By the year 2040, there will be an estimated 600 million university students worldwide. On campuses, the belief that life is meaningless and secular is also rapidly growing, leading to notable degrees of brokenness and social ills, such as, depression, anxiety, addiction, and hopelessness. Coupled with these trends, collegiate ministries commissioned with bringing the hope of the Gospel to campuses often struggle to develop and expand their teams, programs, and overall mission to meet growing demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transplanters</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/transplanters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/transplanters/</guid>
      <description>Transplanters enables pioneering non-profit leaders to take the next step in their growth and development. These leaders are pioneers because they sacrifice everything in pursuit of their innovative ideas. Transplanters serves these leaders by performing development services including grant writing and consulting on organizational structure, systems, and priorities.
In addition, Transplanters serves foundations by providing exceptional project management and reporting, as well as the opportunity to align with well-managed, highly-influential non-profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Or More</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/twoormore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/twoormore/</guid>
      <description>For decades, a those who identify as bi/multi-racial have been overlooked within society. Whether in families, neighborhoods, communities of faith, or otherwise, these individuals are often seen as &amp;ldquo;half&amp;rdquo; of one idenity and &amp;ldquo;half&amp;rdquo; of another, and as such are rarely fully embraced. This &amp;ldquo;half existence&amp;rdquo; leads to bullying, disillusionment, poor mental health, and a host of other issues that do not reflect God&amp;rsquo;s desires for their lives, which is all the more concerning when one considers that those who identify as bi/multi-racial will be the majority of people in the United States by 2040.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beautiful baptism for a dear friend.</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/blog/vivamus-lacus-mauris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 06:12:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/blog/vivamus-lacus-mauris/</guid>
      <description>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Impedit, rerum voluptates veniam. Esse, nihil, ea, eaque, quos cum id tempore voluptate nisi nemo debitis impedit officiis culpa repellat voluptatum in aperiam error quo minima ratione ex pariatur maxime eligendi dolore nesciunt molestiae enim alias atque commodi delectus perferendis. Blanditiis, iste placeat nostrum in! Eligendi, omnis, unde, quos ullam nesciunt molestias quis a saepe nisi distinctio molestiae voluptate obcaecati officiis consequuntur similique aspernatur rerum sequi placeat iure quaerat itaque libero officia recusandae ad corrupti aperiam cum beatae.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application development</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom website design</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO &amp; SEM services</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress integration</title>
      <link>https://abide.community/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abide.community/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think they tried to market it to the billionaire, spelunking, base-jumping crowd. i did the same thing to gandhi, he didn&amp;rsquo;t eat for three weeks. i once heard a wise man say there are no perfect men.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
